Finding Aid for the Edwin Wendell Pauley Papers, 1907-2001
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
- Memorabilia
  - 3 Drinking Glasses with 717 No Highland Ave - EWP - LA CAL 54 frosted lettering (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - First Men on the Moon $5 Commemorative Coin Issued by the Republic of the Marshall Islands (Box 132, Folder 1)
    6 sets
  - National Rifle Association Junior Division Pin - Marksman (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Metal Pin (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Broken case
  - One Use Tooth Brush Packet with Chaarl Tooth Powder (Box 133, Folder 5)
- News Clippings
  - San Francisco Chronicle (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Oversized; Photocopy; More in b64_f1
  - UC News - Pauley's 32 Years as UC Regent (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Oversized; Vol. 47, No. 26
  - Los Angeles Times Opinion - Truman Assured History Role, Clara Boothe Luce Believes (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rancheros Visitadores Silver Anniversary (Box 90, Folder 7)
    Includes Booklets and Newsletter
  - Scouts - Harold Pauley Memorial (Box 90, Folder 8)
    Includes Correspondence, Booklets, and Newsletters
  - Miscellaneous files from office (Box 90, Folder 9)
    Includes Correspondence
  - Ballroom Dedication for Bobbe at University of California, Berkeley - March 17. 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Includes Correspondence and Booklets
  - Harry S. Truman Library (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Includes Correspondence, Booklets, and Pamphlets
  - Commencement of the University of Santa Clara (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Includes Booklet
  - George Pepperdine College (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Includes Booklet and Memorabilia
  - Edwin W. Pauley Collection of Western Americana (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Includes Correspondence and Booklet
  - President Harry S. Truman (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Includes Photographs, Correspondence, and Booklets
  - V.I.P. Letters (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Important Letters (Box 91, Folder 8)
    Includes Correspondence and Magazine Clippings
  - Occidental College (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Includes Correspondence and Booklets; f. 1 of 2
  - Occidental College (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Includes Correspondence and Booklets; f. 2 of 2
  - Democratic Convention (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Mexico Items (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Includes Photographs and Correspondence
  - Nazli (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Includes Booklet; Includes Hollywood Monthly Magazine, Vol. 1 Nos. 5, 6, 7, 8
  - Jordan (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Includes Tastevin En Main, No. 20; Time Magazine, April 2, 1956, Vol. 67, No. 14; the Diners' Club News, Vol. 6, Issue 5
  - Presidents' Folder (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Includes Photographs, Correspondence and Magazines
  - EWP - copies of Man of the Week (Box 92, Folder 8)
    10 copies
  - Stuart Symington (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Sports (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Regents File - UCLA (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Social Clippings (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Harry S. Truman (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Texas Oil (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Reparations (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Chairman Board Regents and Rubber Deal Million Dollar Suit (Box 93, Folder 8)
    Includes California Monthly, Vol. 66, No. 9
  - Los Angeles Rams (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Oil (Box 93, Folder 10)
    Includes The Party Line, Vol. 13, No. 2
  - Pauley Stations, Inc. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    Includes Correspondence, Pamphlets, and Memorabilia
  - Wendell Phillips, Leader of University of California African Expedition (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Mexico (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - 25th Wedding Anniversary, Dinner given by Perle Mesta, Ernie Kovaks, and Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Edmund G. "Pat" Brown with EWP (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Berkeley Daily Gazette with EWP and JFK (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Rick, Susan, and Legal Reserve Life (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Biography of Elbert L. Pauley from Pasadena Community Book, 1947 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Photocopy
  - Correspondence of Edward H. Siems of the Grand Lodge Free and Accepted Mason of California with Roy Jackson Henville (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence of Clyde Hubbell of the Pasadena Policemen's Relief Association with EWP (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Bobbe (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - S.F. Examiner - Why Pauley Let Reeves Take Rams (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Times - View Section (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Red Skelton front page?
  - Beverly Hills People (Box 94, Folder 11)
    Vol. 4, No. 30; 3 copies
  - Artist Vasa as guest honor at Art Museum Council Reception at the Regency Club (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Bobbe - Arts and Museums (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Certificate of Edwin Wendell Pauley, Jr. appointed at First Lieutenant, Transportation Corps (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - EWP and family in the news - Social (Box 94, Folder 15)
    Includes photocopies of news clippings
  - Children's Research Institute of California (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Social Events (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Social Events - 1984 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Social Events - 1984 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    Includes Correspondence; f. 2 of 2
  - From Paul Singh to Bobbe Re: Susan Pauley's wedding (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Social Events - 1985 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Social Events - 1985 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    Includes Correspondence; f. 2 of 2; Includes Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Graphic Arts Council, Spring 1985, Vol. 15, No. 11
  - Social Events - 1986 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Social Events - 1986 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    Includes Photograph, Newsletter, Magazine Clippings; f. 2 of 2
  - EWP Business and Politics (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Nomination for Undersecretary of the Navy (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - EWP's Withdrawal of Nomination to be Undersecretary of the Navy (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Oily Pauley Quits Under Fire (Box 95, Folder 21)
    State Labor News, Vol. 2, No. 39
  - Harry S. Truman (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Television and First Telecast (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Catalina, the 'West Coast Bermuda' (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Solemn Tribute Paid to War Dead on Armistice Day (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Gold Cup Day (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Potsdam Papers (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - EWP as Chairman of UC Regents (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Need More Tourist Hotels Here, Survey Indicates by Gerry Burtnett - Advertiser (Box 99, Folder 8)
    Copy
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - EWP on North Korea (July 1950) (Box 117, Folder 1)
    News Clippings
  - Uno Cincuenta (Box 121, Folder 9)
    Oversized; No. 716
  - EWP Scrapbook (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Times Opinion - Truman: Rock Amid Change (Box 122, Folder 8)
    Oversized; 8 copies; Enlarged and on illustration board
  - Seasons - Advertising supplement to the Los Angeles Times (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - EWP and Bobbe in the news (Box 144, Folder 2)
- News Clippings Albums
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 109, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Includes correspondence and Presidential memorabilia
  - Sessions and Caminita Public Relations Counsel (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings on EWP (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Personal
  - Coconut Island Hotel Blueprint (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Oversized; Includes correspondence
  - Caricature of EWP (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - EWP - upon retiring as UC Regent (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Scrapbook
  - Correspondence with Colonel R.L. Harrison (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - California Democratic Congressional Ball (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Dinner - G. Wyman - 10/6/72 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, News Clippings
  - Democratic Associates (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Congressional Dinner - June 26, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention - July 1972 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, News Clippings, Magazines
  - Assembly Democratic Caucus (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Honorable Mike Mansfield Dinner - January 2, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Honorable Luther Hodges Dinner - March 7, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Photographs, Correspondence
  - Democratic Associates Inc. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Honorable Order of Kentucky Colonels (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Appreciation Letters from EWP (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Correspondence; f. 1 of 2
  - Appreciation Letters from EWP (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Correspondence; f. 2 of 2
  - Letters of Congratulations to and from EWP (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Appreciation Letters to EWP (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Honorable John F. Kennedy (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - President Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, News Clippings, Booklet
  - Letters of Recommendation (Political) (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Election 1964 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Honorable Edmund G. Brown Testimonial Dinner (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Booklet
  - General Correspondence - A (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence - B (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence - C (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence - D (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence - E (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence - P (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence - "P" (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence - Q (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Edwin Pauley Jr II (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Pauley Family (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Edwin W. Pauley, Jr. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, Booklets
  - Harold R. Pauley (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Personal Priority Certificates (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Adventure (Boat purchased from Harry Earnshaw) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Sidney P. Allen (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Bank Data (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Cannell and Chaffin, Inc. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - State of Colorado - General (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Check requests (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Airline Data (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Memorabilia
  - Cousin Flossie Maxwell (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Correspondence; Includes photographs of EWP and family
  - Los Angeles Times and National Oil Derrick (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Telegram from Vince Flaherty (Box 59, Folder 9)
    Correspondence; Copy
  - Coconut Island Club International (Box 59, Folder 17)
    Pamphlet
  - Coconut Island Long Range Development Plan (Box 59, Folder 18)
    Bound Manuscript and Correspondence
  - Bishop Museum (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Letters from Martha McHenry to daughter Ora Condrey (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Photocopy from the University of California Centennial Pictorial History (Box 60, Folder 1)
    pg. 270
  - St. Louis Post-Dispatch re: Edwin W. Pauley's Record (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Pauley Group Leaves for Island Paradise (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - California Monthly (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Magazine; pg. 21
  - Council on Activities - Bobbe Jean McHenry (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Twenty Five Year Club of the Petroleum Industry membership certificate (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Memorabilia
  - Georgia Military Academy Distinguished Alumnus certificate (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - EWP and Bobbe with General and Mrs. Mark Clark - Honolulu Star-Bulletin (Box 60, Folder 8)
    News Clippings; Mainly About People section
  - EWP and Bobbe with Robert Gordon Sproul and Mrs. Sproul - UCLA Alumni Magazine (Box 60, Folder 9)
    Magazine Clippings
  - EWP and Bobbe with William Boyle, Mrs. Luckey, and Senator George Luckey (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Where - Where What When in Chicago (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Magazine
  - C. Andrade, III check to EWP (Box 60, Folder 12)
    Check no. 2826
  - Los Amigos des Pueblo Bicentennial Keepsake Album - Governor's Ball (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Biographies of EWP (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Reparations and Paris Peace Conference (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, Booklets, News Clippings, and Photographs; Includes Current Biography Who's News and Why, Vol. 6, no. 6
  - Los Angeles World Affairs Council seating place card (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Wedding card from Robert A. McHenry to Ora and John Condrey (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Kentucky Cycle (The) (Box 60, Folder 18)
    News Clippings; Includes one photocopy
  - Memoirs of Petrol Pete (The) (Box 60, Folder 19)
    Bound news clippings in a book
  - Invitation (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Miss Dewline - polar bear cub (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Are You There, Australia? - Voice goes 17,000 miles in phone link (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Seasons Greetings from William D. Simmons (Box 60, Folder 23)
    Sec't to Kennedy?
  - Passing in Review - Georgia Military Academy (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Edwin Pauley Jr. and Miss Zell Russell at St. John's Hospital ball (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Nixon Party (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Muses luncheon honoring Lt. Commander Rose Escobedo (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Correspondence and Photographs
  - From Margie Kim to Bobbe - UCLA College of Letters and Science Awards Dinner (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Bobbe with John Lithgow, Rue Pine, Raymond and Eva Orbach (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - From Elaine Smoots to Bobbe - Bobbe with Robert Merill (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Special Occasion cards from friends and family (Box 61, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, Photographs, Cards, and Postcards
  - Camera, TV, and Binocular booklets (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - To Mrs. Pauley from Lilla Perry (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - 1951 General Correspondence - B (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Photographs, and News Clippings
  - 1950 General Correspondence - B (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - C (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - D (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - E (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - F (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - G (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - H (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - I (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - J (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - K (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - 1950 General Correspondence - L (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Magazine Clippings, and News Clippings; f. 1 of 2
  - 1950 General Correspondence - L (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, Magazine Clippings, and News Clippings; f. 2 of 2
  - Index to EWP's Personal Files (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Autograph Requests (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Congratulatory Lists (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Sheridan Downey - General correspondence and miscellaneous data (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Lawrence Radiation Laboratory - University of California, Berkeley (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Photographs, Booklets, and Magazines
  - General Correspondence - J (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence - K (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence - M (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence - M (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence - "M" (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Correspondence and News Clippings; f. 1 of 2
  - General Correspondence - "M" (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Correspondence and News Clippings; f. 2 of 2
  - Cecil R. King (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Louisiana Delta Lands (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Program for National Security (A) (Box 72, Folder 5)
    2 copies; Report of the President's Advisory Commission on Universal Training
  - Robert A. Taft Memorial (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Speeches - San Diego Remarks regarding Democratic Associates (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Speeches - Remarks Following Senator McClellan's Speech (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Pepperdine's Freedom Forum, Biltmore, June 23rd
  - Speeches - Kentucky Colonel Banquet (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Speeches - President's Committee on Education Beyond High School (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Speeches - UCLA Phi Psi - 8/31/56 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Speeches - Hollywood Bowl Presentation (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Speeches - UCLA School of Business Administration (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Speeches - Address Honoring President Robert G. Sproul (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Speeches - Boy Scout (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Democratic National Committee (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Central Committee - Los Angeles County (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - 1952 Election - General (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, Booklets, Pamphlets, Magazines, and News Clippings; f. 1 of 3
  - 1952 Election - General (Box 73, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, Booklets, Pamphlets, Magazines, and News Clippings; f. 2 of 3
  - 1952 Election - General (Box 73, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, Booklets, Pamphlets, Magazines, and News Clippings; f. 3 of 3
  - Hotel Reservations (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - F (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - G (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, Postcards, Magazine Clippings, and News Clippings
  - 1952 General Correspondence - H (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - I (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Inter-Office Memorandums (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - J (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - K (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - L (Box 74, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Memorabilia, Magazine Clippings, and News Clippings
  - 1952 General Correspondence - Mc (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - M (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, Booklets, Pamphlets, and News Clippings
  - 1952 General Correspondence - N (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - O (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Correspondence and Booklets
  - 1952 General Correspondence - P (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - R (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Rams - Los Angeles - General (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Rams - Los Angeles - General (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 1952 General Correspondence - S (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, Booklets, Magazine Clippings, and News Clippings; f. 1 of 2
  - 1952 General Correspondence - S (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, Booklets, Magazine Clippings, and News Clippings; f. 2 of 2
  - 1952 General Correspondence - T (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - EWP and family - Social (Box 94, Folder 16)
    Photographs, Correspondence, and Magazine Clipping
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 94, Folder 17)
    Magazine; Vol. 20, No. 4
  - 1975 Pacific Southwest Open Tennis Championships (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - In Memoriam of Edwin Wendell Pauley (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 94, Folder 20)
    Magazine; Vol. 11, No. 2
  - Pacific Oil World (Box 94, Folder 21)
    Magazine; Vol. 74, Nos. 11 and 12
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 1)
    Magazine; Vol. 11, No. 3
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 2)
    Magazine; Vol. 11, No. 5
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 3)
    Magazine; Vol. 11, No. 9
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 4)
    Magazine; Vol. 11, No. 1
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - ARCS Foundation (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Club & Sports Society (Box 95, Folder 12)
    Magazine; Vol. 32, No. 12
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 15)
    Magazine; Vol. 14, No. 5
  - Celebrity-Society (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Hollywood Life (Box 95, Folder 18)
    Magazine; Vol. 5, No. 30
  - Letter from EWP to Edwin Pauley Jr (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Letter from EWP to Edwin Pauley Jr (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Letter from EWP to Edwin Pauley Jr (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - TIME (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - TIME (Box 96, Folder 21)
    Magazine; Vol. 39, No. 24
  - TIME (Box 96, Folder 22)
    Magazine; Vol. 46, No. 31
  - Letters from EWP to Edwin W. Pauley, Jr. (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Letters from EWP to Bobbe (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Letter to EWP and Bobbe from H. H. Arnent? (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - EWP with Gary Cooper and Veronica Balfe (Box 97, Folder 10)
    Photographs
  - UCLA Weekly including photograph of Charles E. Young, Mrs. Young, Charles J. Hitch, Mrs. Hitch, EWP, and Bobbe (Box 97, Folder 11)
    Newsletter; Vol. 2, No. 16
  - Letter from Claude Pepper to Bobbe (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Letter from Frances Perkins to Bobbe (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Telegram to EWP from Ora, John, Joanne, and Mother (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Letter from Frank Walker to EWP and Bobbe (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - California Museum of Science and Industry Parking Pass (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Fifty Year Award presented by Grand Lodge Free and Accepted Masons of the State of California (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Gold Nameplate - Edwin W. Pauley (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Engraved frame for Bobbe and EWP from Betty and Bill for 25th anniversary (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Ninety-Fifth Commencement, University of California - Dialogue book (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Speech note cards for dedication of Sproul Hall and for presentation of Doctorate of Law to Robert Gordon Sproul (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Appointment book and daily memoranda (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - UCLA Memorial Activities Center Founders' Club metal plates (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Regent - University of California Identification Card from the Office of the Secretary of State (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-Second Commencement, University of California at Los Angeles - Dialogue book (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Edwin W. Pauley Foundation Endorsed Scholars Program - 1996 Report UCLA College of Letters and Science (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - 1994 College of Letters and Science Awards Dinner Invitations and Program Booklets (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - 1994 College of Letters and Science Awards Dinner Correspondence, Speeches, and Programs (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - EWP - Doctorate of Law degree from George Pepperdine College (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - EWP - Doctorate of Letters degree from the University of Santa Clara (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Authenticated Translation of Sorge's Own Story (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - EWP and Bobbe's Guests Book (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - UCLA University Village Child Care Complex - Children's Artwork and Photo Album (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Award for Barbara M. Pauley Pagen presented by Friends of UCLA Child Care Services (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - EWP Elected as Chairman of UC Board of Regents Album (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Correspondence and News Clippings
  - Miscellaneous Pages of Photographs, Correspondence, Telegrams, Invitations, Greeting Cards, and News Clippings (Box 101, Folder 2)
    Oversized; Scrapbook; Includes Bobbe's Russian Passport
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, Correspondence, Telegrams, Invitations, Greeting Cards, and News Clippings (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - JFK and Ted Kennedy (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - X-ray of EWP by Carl H. Parker, M.D. and John F. Chapman, M.D. (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Harry S. Truman 20 cent stamps (Box 117, Folder 2)
    16 Stamps total
  - Brown and Jefferies Portrait Unveiling Ceremonies (Box 117, Folder 3)
    Book with slip case
  - Dr. Armand Hammer 85th Birthday at Los Angeles County Museum of Art with concert by Maestro Mstislac Rostropovich (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Photo Book
  - Truman Presidency (The) - Legacy of Leadership (A) (Box 117, Folder 5)
    2 program booklets
  - La Encina - Occidental College (Box 117, Folder 6)
    Yearbook
  - Nurnberg by Charles W. Alexander (Box 117, Folder 7)
    Book
  - Silver Key to Harold Pauley Boy Scouts Memorial Hall and Newsletter (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Focus on Dr. John H. Lawrence and the Donner Lab - Roche Medical Image (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Oversized; Magazine, Vol. 6 No. 3; More in b70_f7
  - 1950 General Correspondence - C (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Oversized; Correspondence and News Clippings; More in b68_f3
  - Mirror (The) (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Oversized; Newspaper; More in b68_f1
  - Los Angeles Orphanage Guild Maryvale (Box 121, Folder 6)
    Oversized; Newspapers
  - Social Events - 1986 - Beverly Hills [213] (Box 121, Folder 7)
    Oversized; Magazines; More in b95_f13
  - EWP to Barbara Jean for their Eighteenth Wedding Anniversary (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Coconut Island Guard (Box 121, Folder 14)
    Oversized; 16 copies
  - From Mike Hayman of the University of California, Berkeley to Bobbe Jean (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - 36th Fighter-Bomber Wing US Air Force (Book) (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - BG (0-22); Cathie Hearst (22-72); Coblentz (72-133); Reagan (145-170); Bill Smith? (172- 195; EWP (205-506); Bobbe 508-514); BG Music? (Box 128, Folder 5)
    Magnetic Tape